

My web portfolio

Contact:

Nicomendoza.92@gmail.com +34644053023

Social Media:

<u>Linkedin</u> Github

LENGUAGES SKILLS

Native: Spanish English: Professional

FRONTEND

Typescript, JavaScript, NextJS, React, CSS, Tailwind, Bootstrap, Shadon.

BACKEND

Node JS, Python, Express and SSR

DATA BASES

Mongo DB, PostgreSQL, mySQL, Supabase, NeonDb, proficiency in Prisma as ORM.

DESIGN

Figma, Full Responsive design, UX and UI experience. Corel draw and adobe XD for fit images and videos.

OTHER INTERSTING FACTS

Full Stack Developer (2021)
Six Sigma White Belt Training and
Certification (2020)
Proficiency in **CRM** and **ERP** platforms
Salesforce/Hubspot/ SAP
R3/Odoo/Oracle WMS Cloud

WORKING SKILLS

Strategic Thinking and Global Vision. Ethics, honesty and responsibility. Flexibility and adaptability. Enjoy solving problems. Planning and Negotiation Skills. Teamwork and proactivity. Initiative and curiosity. Multitasking and adaptability to dynamic environments.

NICOLAS MENDOZA

ABOUT ME

I am a freelance developer with 3 years of experience creating custom web solutions and applications. I have worked on projects such as inventory management systems, financial management platforms, e-commerce applications, landing pages, and I am currently developing new applications based on the specific requirements of my clients. My focus is on delivering efficient solutions tailored to business needs.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SaaS builded

2024 - current

Management System - info

Technologies: Next JS – typescript – Prisma, Neon, clerk, SSR, NodeJs.

The platform allows you to generate detailed reports, view interactive graphs and receive real-time notifications. It is designed to optimize business management and provide key decision-making tools. In addition, it is intuitive and adaptable to the specific needs of users.

Full Stack Developer - ALLCOT GROUP

Sept 2022 to April 2024

Implementation of carbon credit platform with IT team

Typescript, JavaScript, Node JS with React as main framework.

Work review and sprint management in projects.

Use of agile methodologies to achieve project objectives and deliverables.

Use of JIRA for project management.

Use of relational (SQL) and non-relational (MongoDB) databases.

Management of AWS cloud (s3bucket).

Use of Git and GitHub to upload and update projects in different branches

Assistant tutor - Rolling Code Argentina

2021 - 9 months

Assistant tutor in programming school

JS, HTML and CSS review and support

Work review and sprint management in projects.

Use of Kanban platforms for project management.

Content creation for classes

Use of GitHub for task tracking and Trello for student tracking.

My Freelance- projects

Inventory Management - ERP system

Technologies: Next JS - Mongo DB

Creation of a web application for inventory management of carbon credits adjusted for a specific company, tracking transactions (purchase/sale), downloads, users and customer data.

Bakery

Technologies: React JS, Node, Mongo, CSS+

E-commerce creation for Pastry Shop, administration panel and web order management (dates, delivery, stripe payments).

ACADEMIC TRAINING

Degree & Master in Industrial Engineer - 2014-2019 **National University of Tucumán- Argentina** UNT

Full Stack Web developer Rolling Code School - 2020-2023
MERN Stack Certificate
Bootcamp Python PRO
Python Certificate